<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/</guid>
      
        <description>Here are links to the blog posts that I have published on medium:
  When will the Ethereum “Merge” Happen? - Make your own prediction in a few lines of Julia code
  Visualizing Developer Activity via the GitHub API - Can we somehow measure open source love?
  Plotting in the Terminal &amp;ndash; An Unconventional Approach to Data Visualization - Who knew Unicode plots could be so much fun?</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      
        <description>SKILLS / KEYWORDS  Julia, MATLAB, Python Data analysis and visualization, Software design and testing Applied Physics, Algorithms, Modelling, Code development Blockchain analytics  OPEN SOURCE  CoinbaseProExchange.jl CryptoDashApp.jl BitcoinRPC.jl Spotify.jl BTC_blockchain_analytics Spotify_data_analysis Health_data_analysis (Talk at JuliaCon 2022) GitHub_data_analysis CoinGecko_API_analysis  EXPERIENCE Metrology Design Engineer at ASML | 01/2019 – Present  Coordinated several functional investigations leading to key software deliveries for ASML&amp;rsquo;s flagship DUV lithography systems, thus contributing to 2022 net sales of €21.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/literature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/literature/</guid>
      
        <description>Julia I use Julia for most of my coding projects. In case you are interested to learn more, here are some links to get you started:
 Julia in VS Code Introduction to Computational Thinking Types in Julia Dictionaries/Sets in Julia Example of data analysis and visualization using a Pluto notebook Data Science in Julia for Hackers Developing Julia Packages  Useful packages Notebooks  Pluto.jl IJulia.jl  Data analysis and visualization  DataFrames.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      
        <description>Vikas Negi&#39;s personal webpage, hosted via IPFS</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>