<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      
        <description>SKILLS / HIGHLIGHTS Julia, MATLAB, Python, SQL, Bash Data analysis and visualization, Software design and testing CI/CD, GitHub Actions, Artifactory, TIOBE TiCS, Docker Applied Physics, Metrology, Algorithms, Modelling Dashboards, REST APIs, Blockchain analytics EXPERIENCE Metrology Sub-Function Architect at ASML | 01/2023 – Present Designed framework for internal software migration to GitHub, set up CI/CD using GitHub Actions and Artifactory, code quality monitoring using TIOBE TiCS TQI. Responsible for group&amp;rsquo;s (~ 50 engineers) MATLAB architecture roadmap, wrote new design documents for essential software components, supervised timely reviews, and oversaw stakeholder management.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/literature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/literature/</guid>
      
        <description>Style guides Blue: A Style Guide for Julia Semantic Versioning 2.0.0 The Black Code Style Shell Style Guide Selection of some interesting reads Understanding SQL: Getting Started with Window Functions I Switched from Notion to Obsidian — This Is How It Went Code Review Etiquette For The Modern Developer Leaving academia? Think twice before going into data or software. Github Templates: The Smarter Way to Formalize Pull Requests Among Development Teams Why OpenAI’s API Is More Expensive for Non-English Languages Real-Time Crowdedness Predictions for Train Travelers Julia I use Julia for most of my coding projects.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      
        <description>Open-source packages WeatherReport.jl CoinbaseProExchange.jl CryptoDashApp.jl BitcoinRPC.jl Spotify.jl BTC_blockchain_analytics Spotify_data_analysis Health_data_analysis (Talk at JuliaCon 2022) GitHub_data_analysis CoinGecko_API_analysis Academic papers ACS Appl. Energy Mater. 2018, 1, 2, 725-735 Macromol. Theory Simul. 2016, 25, 550–558 J. Polym. Sci. Part B: Polym. Phys. 2016, 54, 2448–2456 Blog posts on Medium Predicting Gas Consumption using Machine Learning in Julia - A data-driven approach to combat the energy crisis
Working with MS SQL Server in Julia - Time to supercharge your data analysis workflow</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      
        <description>Vikas Negi&#39;s personal webpage, hosted via IPFS</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>