<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/</guid>
      
        <description>Here are links to the blogs that I have published on medium:
  Are Your Playlists Groovy Enough? - Let’s find out by using Spotify’s public API along with Julia
  Examining Developer and Community Metrics for Cryptocurrencies - Harness the power of interactive Pluto notebooks
  Analyze Your Health and Fitness Data using Julia - An easy data science project to spice up your coding weekend</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      
        <description>SKILLS/KEYWORDS  Julia, MATLAB, Python Functional data analysis, Data visualization, FN/SW design and testing Applied Physics, Algorithms, Modelling, Code development  EXPERIENCE Functional Design Engineer at ASML | 01/2019 – Present  Coordinated functional investigations leading to key Metro Expose SW deliveries in the following projects: XT:1460 TFH, XT:400L TSH (More than Moore) and XT:860N Developed new design documents for critical SW components, supervised timely reviews, and oversaw stakeholder management Improved cross-functional competence by building knowledge transfer documents, participating in key design reviews Independently supported various critical escalations with customers around the world Involved in coaching junior engineers, supervised team participation in multiple hackathons on a DUV Expose train level  Eindhoven University of Technology | 06/2014 - 09/2018  Computational modeling combined with in-house optical experiments to study phase separation in organic thin films during spin-coating Established and coordinated external collaboration with research groups in Germany, Russia and United States resulting in three publications Proven track record in computational physics with multiple publications in peer-reviewed journals Demonstrated excellent communication skills through talks and posters at various international conferences in Europe and Asia  Shell Technology Centre Bangalore | 05/2013 - 02/2014  Master’s Thesis: Used Density Functional Theory to study methanation on a cobalt catalyst during Fischer-Tropsch synthesis Worked in a multi-disciplinary and cross-functional team of material scientists, computational physicists and geologists Added significant value to computational R&amp;amp;D at Shell, received the highest grade for master’s thesis based on this work  EDUCATION Ph.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      
        <description>This static website is hosted on the InterPlanetary File System or IPFS via Fleek. It makes use of the Hugo framework. I also use an Ethereum Name Service domain to point to this site. It is the first time that I have built a web3 based webpage. Needless to say, I am super excited to explore what this technology has to offer.
Feel free to visit the other tabs on this site, and share some feedback.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      
        <description>Julia I use Julia for most of my coding projects. In case you are interested to learn more, here are some links to get you started:
 Julia in VS Code Introduction to Computational Thinking Types in Julia Dictionaries/Sets in Julia Example of data analysis and visualization using a Pluto notebook Data Science in Julia for Hackers Developing Julia Packages  Useful packages Notebooks  Pluto.jl IJulia.jl  Data analysis and visualization  DataFrames.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      
        <description>I currently work as a Metrology Design Engineer at ASML in the Netherlands. I love coding, and my language of choice is Julia. Besides that, I occasionally tinker with my Raspberry Pi. My other hobbies include listening to podcasts (big fan of Lex Fridman) during long walks, running and watching new shows/documentaries on Netflix. I am also a proud owner of a custom built PC and a Xbox One S. Whenever time permits, I try to learn more about Web 3.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>